<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">iSafe</string>
    <string name="navigation_open">"Open Navigation Drawer"</string>
    <string name="navigation_close">"Close Navigation Drawer"</string>

    <string-array name="text">
        <item>An App By</item>
        <item>PandP Codes</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="about_us_text"><font size="30">What is iSafe?ЁЯШБ\n\n</font>iSafe is a social organisation working with a wide range of urban stakeholders to make public spaces safer and more inclusive for women. We also generate a safety score based on the data we collect and provide it in the iSafe app for users to make safe and informed decisions about their mobility.
    \n\n<font size="30">Our VisionЁЯШЗ\n\n</font>To provide credible data and build vibrant ecosystems for safe, inclusive and accesible cities.
    \n\n<font size="30">OriginsЁЯЩМ\n\n</font>At iSafe, we believe that cities must be made safer and more inclusive for women and everyone. iSafe is a tool that works to enable cities to become safer through collection of data through crowdsourcing and other methods. The Safety Audit, that forms the core of iSafe, assesses different parameters linked to safer and more inclusive public spaces. We were fortunate to have an exceptional advisory board that provided us with comments, experience and ideas to make the Safety Audit rubric a strong and precise tool. We also believe that quantification will help in creating more safety. Having a score for an area provides a simple way to measure improvements.
    \n\n<font size="30">Choice of NameЁЯСС\n\n</font>So why iSafe? A few reasons.<br />
1. The most obvious is that the iSafe mobile safety app shows a safety audit score as a тАЬpinтАЭ on a map.<br />
2. The safety pin is a symbol of something that holds fabric together тАУ stops it from coming apart. Our hope is that our iSafe plays that role тАУ brings together the fabric of our society.
     \n\n<font size="30">ЁЯе░In the end, you are all we care about, because Your Safety Is Our First PriorityЁЯе░</font></string>
    <string name="appwidget_text">EXAMPLE</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">This is an app widget description</string>
    <string name="where_women_are_honoured">рдЬрд╣рд╛рдВ рдирд╛рд░реА рдХрд╛ рд╕рдореНрдорд╛рди рд╣реЛрддрд╛ рд╣реИ рд╡рд╣рд╛рдВ рджреЗрд╡рддрд╛ рдкреНрд░рд╕рдиреНрди рд╣реЛрддреЗ рд╣реИрдВ, рдЬрд╣рд╛рдВ рдЙрдирдХрд╛ рд╕рдореНрдорд╛рди рдирд╣реАрдВ рд╣реЛрддрд╛ рд╡рд╣рд╛рдВ рд╕рднреА рдХрд╛рд░реНрдп рдирд┐рд╖реНрдлрд▓ рд╣реЛ рдЬрд╛рддреЗ рд╣реИрдВред \n- рдордиреБрд╕реНрдореГрддрд┐</string>
    <string name="about_us">рд╣рдорд╛рд░реЗ рдмрд╛рд░реЗ рдореЗрдВ</string>
    <string name="educate">рд╢рд┐рдХреНрд╖рд╛</string>
    <string name="fake_call">рдлрд░реНрдЬреА рдХреЙрд▓</string>
    <string name="contacts">рд╕рдВрдкрд░реНрдХ</string>
    <string name="transport">рдпрд╛рддрд╛рдпрд╛рдд</string>
    <string name="sos">рдЖрдкрд╛рддрдХрд╛рд▓реАрди</string>
    <string name="home">рдШрд░</string>
    <string name="authentication">Authentication</string>
    <string name="logout">рд▓реЙрдЧ рдЖрдЙрдЯ</string>
    <string name="change_language">рднрд╛рд╖рд╛ рдмрджрд▓реЛ</string>
    <string name="english">рдЕрдВрдЧреНрд░реЗрдЬрд╝реА</string>
    <string name="hindi">рд╣рд┐рдиреНрджреА</string>
    <string name="marathi">рдорд░рд╛рдареА</string>
    <string name="sharing">рд╢реЗрдпрд░рд┐рдВрдЧ</string>
    <string name="share">рд╢реЗрдпрд░</string>
</resources>